ledsmagazine.com 2019-12-20

# Privacy Policy | ENDEAVOR BUSINESS MEDIA

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent; however, if you reject cookies, you will not be able to sign in to the Web Sites or take full advantage of our Web Sites and services. Additionally, if you clear all cookies on your browser at any point after setting your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent, you will have to again reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. If you wish, you may disable pixel tags by setting your browser to omit images and disable JavaScript.

You can find more information about cookies and how they work, what cookies have been set on your computer or mobile device and how to manage and delete them at [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) and <http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk>.

When is personally identifiable information collected? How is your

information used?  

Endeavor Business Media collects information by which someone could identify you as a specific, identifiable individual (we refer to this type of information in this Privacy Policy collectively as “Personal Data”) that you choose to provide us when you subscribe to our magazines, sign up for e-newsletters, enter a contest, participate in surveys, login into our Web Sites using a third party login system (including, but not limited to, Facebook Connect, Twitter, etc.), register for a Web Site, webcast, or trade show, or otherwise communicate with us. When you provide this information to us, you are no longer anonymous.

We refer collectively to all information we collect that is not Personal Data, including usage data collected from cookies, pixels and similar technologies discussed in this Privacy Policy, demographic data and de-identified Personal Data, as "Non-Personal Data". If we combine Non-Personal Data with Personal Data, we will treat the combined information as Personal Data under this Privacy Policy.

​

We may use your contact information to send notices for subscription renewal or provide you with information about products or services you have ordered with us. We may also use your contact information to send you e-newsletters or other promotional e-mails that contain targeted, relevant content that may be useful to your business. All promotional e-mails you receive from us will include an option to opt out of similar e-mail communications in the future.

We may include Personal Data, such as your name, address, telephone and fax numbers, and e-mail address, as well as “demographic” information such as the type of business you work for, your job responsibilities and certain information about your company. We will tell you at the time we collect information whether the information requested is necessary for you to participate in a particular feature. The information we collect is used to respond to your specific requests, to send you periodic information and special offers from Endeavor Business Media and our sponsors, to provide you with updates on Endeavor Business Media offerings and features, to provide you with product information from manufacturers in our database, and to provide our sponsors and business partners with data about our users.

We may disclose aggregated information about users and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction. We also reserve the right to disclose your Personal Data if we are required to do so by law, or in the good faith belief that disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process, to respond to claims, or to protect or advance the rights, property, safety, or well-being of our company, our employees, customers, or the public. In the unlikely event that all of Endeavor Business Media’s assets or substantially all of its assets are acquired, then user and customer information, which may include Personal Information, may be one of the transferred assets.

​

We use the information we collect, including Personal Data and Web Site usage data:

​

  * to enable you to use our Web Sites, to create an account or profile, to process information you provide via our Web Sites (including verifying that your email address is active and valid) and to process your transactions;

  * to provide related customer service and care, including responding to your questions, complaints, or comments and sending surveys (with your consent) and processing survey responses;​

  * to provide you with information, products, or services that you have requested;

  * to receive and process job applications for jobs with us;

  * with your consent, to provide you with information, products, or services that we otherwise believe will interest you, including special opportunities from us and our third-party partners;

  * to tailor content, recommendations, and advertisements we and third parties display to you, both on the Web Sites and elsewhere online;

  * for internal business purposes, such as to improve our Web Sites and services;

  * to administer and process contests, sweepstakes, and promotions;

  * to contact you with administrative communications and, in our discretion, changes to our Privacy Policy, Terms and Conditions of Use, or any of our other policies;

  * to comply with regulatory and legal obligations; and

  * for purposes as disclosed at the time you provide your information, with your consent, and as further described in this Privacy Policy.  

How does Endeavor Business Media secure and store your information?

We use reasonable precautions, including appropriate technical, administrative, and physical procedures, to try to protect collected Personal Data from loss, misuse, or alteration.

Many of our Web Sites contain links to Web Sites owned and operated by unaffiliated third parties. These links are provided as a service to you, and do not constitute Endeavor Business Media's endorsement or support of those third parties or their Web Sites. Each third party Web Site has its own information collection and use practices, and we advise you to review their policies.

Endeavor Business Media is not responsible or liable for third party privacy practices or the content of third party sites. We are not responsible or liable for any breach of security or for the actions of these parties.

Due to the design of the Internet and other factors outside our control, we cannot guarantee that communications between you and our servers will be free from unauthorized access by third parties. Any information you provide may be stored and maintained in an Endeavor Business Media database, either housed at Endeavor Business Media or with a third party vendor. In the case of a sale, change of ownership or merger involving Endeavor Business Media or any parent, subsidiary or affiliated company, your information may be transferred to a third party.

Passwords may be used by a Site to protect your personal data. We recommend that you do not share your passwords with anyone, and notify us promptly if you believe your password security has been breached. Endeavor Business Media will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited e-mail. Also, if you are using a computer that others have access to, such as one in a computer lab, Internet cafe or public library, always remember to log out and close your browser window when leaving any of our Sites.

In addition, any personally identifiable information or sensitive data that you choose to disclose through any discussion boards or other public online forums hosted on the Web Sites may be collected and used by others. We recommend caution when giving out personal information to others in these public online forums. When you provide information on these forums, you do so at your own risk. Endeavor Business Media does not take any steps to protect the privacy of information you volunteer about yourself in public forums or other publicly accessible sections of our Web Sites. The information you share may be viewed by any other user of the Web Sites.

We will retain your Personal Data and any information collected from your use of our Web Sites for as long as you are a Subscriber or otherwise maintain a user account on our Web Sites and for a reasonable time thereafter.

What options do you have about how Endeavor Business Media uses or shares your information?

​

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the Personal Data you provide us. To exercise control over your information, we have provided you with the following mechanisms:

If you no longer wish for us to share your mailing address or other contact information with our sponsors or other third parties, you may adjust your account preferences or you can send us an e-mail at [donotdisclose@endeavorb2b.com](mailto:donotdisclose@endeavorb2b.com). For us to be able to locate your record, your e-mail must include your name, mailing address, e-mail address, and must identify the Endeavor Business Media product, event, or service for which you are registered. We will strive to process your request within 10 days, and thereafter we will no longer share your contact information with third parties. Please note that we will not be able to stop third parties from sending you information about their products or services if your information was shared with them before we received your request.

Regarding e-mail specifically, you have the opportunity to elect to stop receiving advertising messages from Endeavor Business Media about our products or services each time you receive such a communication from us. To unsubscribe from such advertising e-mail messages, please follow the directions included in that e-mail message. We will endeavor to process your request within 10 days. Please note that during that time, you may continue to receive e-mail messages from Endeavor Business Media about its products or services.

Additionally, regardless of whether you have unsubscribed from receiving advertising and promotional material from Endeavor Business Media, you will continue to receive transactional information from us, such as information relating to your account or payment or bill information. If you receive broadcast e-mail messages that we may send about third party manufacturers in whose products or services we believe you may be interested, and no longer wish to receive such messages, you can do so by following the directions included in the e-mail message you receive. If you have further questions regarding your options with respect to your account information, please contact us at the e-mail or mailing address included at the beginning of this Privacy Policy.

Your Consent

​

By using our Web Sites, you are consenting to our processing of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. “Processing” means using cookies on a computer or hand held device or using or touching information in any way, including, but not limited to, collecting, storing, deleting, using, combining and disclosing information, all of which activities will take place in the United States. If you reside outside the United States your information will be transferred, processed and stored there under United States privacy standards.

​

How Can I Access, Correct, or Amend Information About Me?​

​

We want to assure you that you have access to your Personal Data that we collect and store. Customers may correct or amend information that is inaccurate by reviewing and updating your account preferences or by contacting us by email at [DPO@Endeavorb2b.com](mailto:DPO@Endeavorb2b.com) or by mail at Endeavor Business Media, Attention: Data Privacy Officer, 1233 Janesville Avenue, Fort Atkinson, Wisconsin 53538.

​

Collection and Use of Information from Children?​

​

Our Web Sites are not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on the Website. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on this Website or on or through any of its features. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please send an email to: [DPO@Endeavorb2b.com](mailto:DPO@Endeavorb2b.com). You may also call 800-547-7377 and ask for the Data Privacy Officer, or mail your request to the attention of the Data Privacy Officer at 1233 Janesville Ave, Fort Atkinson, WI 53538.

Regarding SSL

​

Our Site uses ‘SSL’ to protect Personal Data. By using a browser that supports security functions, when you access to our Web Sites and enter Personal Data, including your name and e-mail address, this information is transferred to our server and the information is automatically encrypted when transmitted and received by servers. Therefore if the transmitted data is intercepted by a third party, there is no need to worry about the content being stolen.

If you use a browser that does not support SSL, you may not be able to access our Web Site or input information.

Do Not Track Signals

​

Your browser may offer you a “Do Not Track” option, which allows you to signal to operators of Web Sites and web applications and services (including behavioral advertising services) that you do not wish such operators to track certain of your online activities over time and/or across different Web Sites. Our Web Sites do not support Do Not Track requests at this time, which means that we collect information about your online activity while you are using our Web Sites.

​

California Privacy Rights

​

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 allows California residents to request certain information regarding disclosure of information to our affiliates and third parties for direct marketing purposes and providing contact information for any such affiliates and third parties. As outlined in this Privacy Policy, we do not share personally identifiable information with any affiliate or third party for direct marketing purposes without your prior approval. If you are a California resident and would like us to confirm in writing that we have not provided any of your Personal Information (as that term is defined in the California Civil Code Sections referenced immediately above) during your use of the Web Sites to any affiliate or third parties for direct marketing purposes, please submit a written request to us at Endeavor Business Media, Attention: Data Privacy Officer, 1233 Janesville Avenue, Fort Atkinson, Wisconsin 53538.

​

Users Outside of the United States and Consent to Transfer

​

The Web Sites and services provided by Endeavor Business Media are operated in the United States. If you are located in another jurisdiction, please be aware that information you provide to us will be transferred to, stored and processed in the United States. By using the Web Sites or providing us with any information, you consent to this transfer, processing, and storage of your information in the United States, a jurisdiction in which the privacy laws are not as comprehensive as those in the country where you reside or are a citizen, such as the European Union. You understand that the U.S. government can obtain access to the Personal Data you submit if necessary for investigative purposes (e.g., terrorism investigation). We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We use appropriate and suitable safeguards for transferring your Personal Data to the U.S.

​

Your EU Data Subject Rights

​

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), we collect and process Personal Data about you only where we have a legal basis for doing so under applicable data protection law, including under the  European General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). The legal bases will depend on the purpose for which we process your Personal Data. This means we collect and use your Personal Data only where:

​

  * We need it to provide the services including to operate the Web Site

  * provide customer support and personalized features and to protect the safety and security of the Web Site

  * It satisfies a legitimate interest (which is not overridden by your rights and interests), such as for research and development, to market and promote the Web Site and to protect our legal rights and interests

  * You give us consent to do so for a specific purpose

  * We need to process your Personal Data to comply with a legal obligation.

​

If you have consented to our use of Personal Data about you for a specific purpose, you have the right to change your preferences at any time.

​

We may use your email address to send you newsletters or marketing emails. We will ask for your consent consistent with the applicable law when you first provide your Personal Data. You can opt out by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails, or you can contact us at [DPO@Endeavorb2b.com](mailto:DPO@Endeavorb2b.com) or in writing to Endeavor Business Media, Attention: Data Privacy Officer, 1233 Janesville Avenue, Fort Atkinson, Wisconsin 53538.

​

Requesting access to your Personal Data.

​

You have the right to request access to any Personal Data we hold about you as well as related information, including the purposes for processing the Personal Data, the recipients or categories of recipients with whom the Personal Data has been shared, where possible, the period for which the Personal Data will be stored, the source of the personal information, and the existence of any automated decision making.

​

Requesting correction of your Personal Data.

You have the right to obtain without undue delay the rectification of any inaccurate Personal Data we hold about you.  

Requesting erasure of your Personal Data.

​

You have the right to request that Personal Data held about you is deleted.

Requesting restriction of processing your Personal Data.

You have the right to prevent or restrict processing of your Personal Data.

Requesting transfer of your Personal Data.

​

You have the right to request transfer of Personal Data directly to a third party where this is technically feasible.  

Where you believe that we have not complied with our obligation under this privacy policy or European data protection law, you have the right to make a complaint to an EU Data Protection Authority, such as the UK Information Commissioner’s Office.

Document History.

​

March 4, 2011 Enacted

May 25th, 2018 Amended

August 5, 2019 Amended

For any questions about this policy, please direct to our data privacy officer at [DPO@Endeavorb2b.com](mailto:DPO@Endeavorb2b.com) or in writing to Endeavor Business Media, Attention: Data Privacy Officer, 1233 Janesville Avenue, Fort Atkinson, Wisconsin 53538.
